const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: '2 + 2?',   // questions[0].question
    answers: ['1','2','3','4'],
    correct: '4'   // questions[0].correct
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: '4 + 2?',  // questions[1].question
    answers: ['13','5','6','4'],
    correct: '6'
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: '100 - 36',
    answers: ['32','64','100','36'],
    correct: '64'
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '25 / 5',
    answers: ['50','25','5','1'],
    correct: '5'
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: '5 * 5',
    answers: ['50','125','100','40'],
    correct: '125'
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: '1000 - 10',
    answers: ['999','990','1000','1110'],
    correct: '990'
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: '2^10',
    answers: ['4096','256','512','1024'],
    correct: '1024'
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: '8 * 8',
    answers: ['125','49','55','64'],
    correct: '64'
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: '4 * 3',
    answers: ['6','18','12','13'],
    correct: '12'
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: '1234 + 1234',
    answers: ['2468','2466','1234','4321'],
    correct: '2468'
  },
];

export default questions;